PARICHART PINIT

Aliss Condominium Tower B 64/330 M.1 Taladkwan, Maung, Nonthaburi, Thailand 11000 Phone: +6687-538-6137

famt.sz@gmail.com

SUMMARY

I am a business analyst with a flair for solving complex business problems adhering to fundamentals of software engineering and loads of creativity. I excel in both technical (VoIP, Linux, Networking, Mini CRM, and programming) and consultation side of the business with experience in interacting with clients and making presentations to senior executives.

Experienced in:

- Requirements gathering, analysis, solution design.
- Creating work order estimates, Proof of Concept demos, bench marking and solution comparisons.
 - Leading and being part of cross functional teams.
 - Presales strategic planning.
 - Work and coordinate with all parties concerned.

Fluency in both English and Thai. I am a personable team player and a firm believer in delivering high quality work efficiently. My colleagues describe me as approachable, enthusiastic, resourceful and helpful. I enjoy working in multicultural work environments as I am a believer in continuous learning.

COMPUTER SKILLS

Software : MS Office, Visio, vTigerCRM, NotePad++, Dreamweaver, PHPMyAdmin

Languages: PHP, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX, JSON.

Databases : MySQL

Platforms: Microsoft Windows (XP/7/8), Linux **Networking Skills:** NAT, Routing and Switching

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Date of Birth: August 4th, 1987 Age : 28 years old : Female : Excellent Sex Health **Nationality** : Thai **Religion**: Buddhist Height : 160 cms. Weight : 52 kgs.

EDUCATION

2006-2009 4th year student, Bachelor Degree of Science, Major Computer Science, Kasetsart

University

COURSE

- Cisco Certified Network Associate (CCNA)
- Big Data and Analytics



WORK EXPERIENCE

Jun 2015 – Present (9 months)

Business Analyst

Ecartstudio Co.,Ltd

- Requirements gathering and design solutions.
- Defining and documenting customer business functions and processes.
- Coordinate with sales team and development team to propose solutions and realize of a certain method to demonstrate by Proof of Concept (POC).
- Coordinate with sales team to propose solutions and estimate man days.
- Coordinate with project managers, system analysts and development team for following processes.

Jan 2014 - May 2015 (1 year 3 months)

Solution Consultant Terabyte Net Solution Public Co.,Ltd

- Requirements gathering and design solutions.
- Presentation and consulting products to clients.
- Analyze and design the best solution as clients' requirements.
- Create a bills of materials (BOM) and design a solution diagram.
- Associate with sales team and development team to propose solutions and influence the clients against the competitors by using several strategic methods, For example, Proof of Concept (POC), presentation and solution comparison.
- Associate with involved teams for total solutions.
- Estimate Man days for implementation.
- Handle the tasks by using vTiger CRM.

Nov 2012 - Dec 2013 (1 year 2 months)

Software Engineer Terabyte Net Solution Public Co.,Ltd

- Developed web interface of IP Telephony system based on Asterisk engine.
- Developed by OOP Architecture.
- Supported, Implement and Maintenance system and software.
- Designed structure and MySQL database.

Oct 2011 - Nov 2012 (1 year 2 months)

Network Programmer

Codetech Co.,Ltd

- Designing and Coding system for company.(PHP)
- Updating and support company website.
- Set up Elastix system by Linux.
- Support VoIP system (Elastix, A2Billing).

May 2010 - Sep 2011 (1 year 5 months)

PHP Programmer

Atapy Co.,Ltd

- Designing and Coding softwares and Web Based Applications for clients. The most of clients are government agencies.
- Designing MySQL database.